

OLEKSANDR LUKHANIN

Frontend React developer

email 🔁 oleksandr.lukhanin@gmail.com

C phone +380 63 419 58 26 telegram Xander_UZZZER

viber +380 63 419 58 26 skype xander_uzzzer

in linkedin linkedin.com/in/oleksandr-lukhanin/

n github github.com/XanderUZZZER

address Kharkiv, Ukraine

PROFILE

Well motivated software developer with solid knowledge of JS (ES6), HTML5, CSS3. Experience with React, Redux +1 year. Good understanding of backend development principles (authentication, middlewares, REST API). Have basic knowledge of TypeScript, C#, .NET Core framework and ASP.NET Core. Able to effectively self-manage during independent projects , as well as collaborate as part of a productive team. Strongly interested in improving skills in fullstack development, backend development and gaining experience with modern web frameworks. Will be glad to be involved in new technology stack

EXPERIENCE

SweetSoft INC. (web, mobile and software development) January 2021 - till now, Kharkiv, Ukraine

Frontend/Fullstack Developer (React/Redux/ASP.NET Core) (development of web application in the field of insurance and data analysis)

Self Employed (developing pet projects)

July 2020 - December 2020, Kharkiv, Ukraine

Frontend/Fullstack Developer (React/Redux/Express)

Biopromin LTD (designing, developing and manufacturing non-invasive medical devices) November 2006 - December 2020, Kharkiv, Ukraine

- CTO
- Quality Manager
- Tech support Engineer
- Designer

SKILLS

ReactJS Hooks API HTML/CSS JavaScript(ES6) Redux Express TypeScript C# .NET Core ASP.NET Core MongoDB MVC **REST API** SQL **SOLID** Git English - Intermediate

EDUCATION

KHARKIV NATIONAL UNIVERSITY OF RADIO ELECTRONICS

FACULTY OF AUTOMATICS AND COMPUTERIZED TECHNOLOGIES

Master's Degree in Manufacturing of Electronics, skill – Engineer of Banking Systems

2004 - 2009, Kharkiv, Ukraine

IT Cloud Academy

IT Cloud Academy Career certification

Certified associate in C# and .NET

March 2017 - July 2017, Kharkiv, Ukraine

PORTFOLIO PROJECTS*

* Due to demo reasons and Heroku (hosting platform) free terms, if an app receives no web traffic in a 30-minute period, it will sleep. Therefore, during the first launch, the application may take longer to load than usual, approximately 15 - 20 seconds. So please be patient and wait for the app to launch. Subsequent launches will be relatively fast

ProShop		DevConnector	
Repo	github.com/XanderUZZZER/proShop	Repo	github.com/XanderUZZZER/dev-connector
Live demo	xander-proshop.herokuapp.com	Live demo	xander-devconnector.herokuapp.com
Stack	React, Hooks API, Redux, Express, JWT, MongoDB	Stack	React, Hooks API, Redux, Express, JWT, MongoDB
	Contact Keeper		ITLogger
Repo	github.com/XanderUZZZER/contact-keeper	Repo	github.com/XanderUZZZER/it-logger
Live demo	xander-contact-keeper.herokuapp.com	Live demo	xander-itlogger.netlify.app
Stack	React, Hooks API, Context API, Express, JWT	Stack	React, Hooks API, Redux, JSON-server
	Github Finder		
Repo	github.com/XanderUZZZER/github-finder		
Live demo	xander-github-finder.netlify.app		
Stack	React, Hooks API, Context API, GitHubAPI		